
MEMORANDUM OF AGREEMENTKnow all Mean by These Presents: 64135003941445MS. RACHELLE N. CAMACHO, MIT College DeanMS. RACHELLE N. CAMACHO, MIT College Dean5601335198120ENGR. RAUL B. GIRONELLA SR., DMin Vice President for Academic AffairsENGR. RAUL B. GIRONELLA SR., DMin Vice President for Academic Affairs-10140956924040${SUPERVISOR_NAME}Officer Head III${SUPERVISOR_NAME}Officer Head III-1968503915410ENGR. OSCAR B. GIRONELLA SR., DMin Executive Vice PresidentENGR. OSCAR B. GIRONELLA SR., DMin Executive Vice President-1034415345440DR. LOURDES S. FERNANDEZPresidentDR. LOURDES S. FERNANDEZPresidentThis Memorandum of Agreement is made entered into and executed by and between:Philippine College of Science and Technology, Calasiao, Pangasinan a Higher Education Institution duly authorized to offer among others, ${COURSE} represented herein by its President, Dr. Lourdes S. Fernandez, hereinafter as PhilCST.and${COMPANY_NAME} represented herein by ${SUPERVISOR_NAME}, Officer Head III.-WITNESSETH-Whereas, PhilCST offer ${COURSE} authorized by the Commission on Higher Education through its Regional Office in San Fernando, La Union;Whereas the students need to be exposed to actual practice in the field of their specialization.Whereas, ${COMPANY_NAME} is under the management of high caliber officials who are professionally competent to provide the said training to all students undergoing ON-THE-JOB TRAININGWhereas, ${COMPANY_NAME} through the leadership of ${SUPERVISOR_NAME}, the said assistance;Now therefore and in coordination of the foregoing premises, the Parties mutually agree to undertake the following roles;ARTICLE IOBLIGATIONS OF PHILCSTCoordinate with the company regarding the schedule of the practicum of the students;Send the students for training with designated Supervisor to monitor their performance with the assistance of an assigned Personnel/Staff;Provide the Personnel/Staff, copies of evaluation form to be used in evaluating the performance of the students; andCommit to the management that the students will abide with the Rules and Regulations of the Company.ARTICLE II${COMPANY_NAME}Accommodate the PhilCST students for their training;Supervise the performance of the students during their practicum;Provide the services of the Personnel/Staff as trainors of the students;Give feedback to the PhilCST through the College Dean/OJT Coordinator on the performance of the students during their training and if necessary, make commendations for the performance of the students who are deservingARTICLE IIILIMITATIONS AND LIABILITIESPhilCST will hold ${COMPANY_NAME} free from or against any claim in relation to the following;Death, injury or disability of the students during the duration of their practicum, andLoss or damage of property of the students while undergoing their practicum.The ${COMPANY_NAME} shall have the right to discontinue the practicum of the students for any misconduct committed which would hamper the efficient operations of the Company after consulting with the PhilCST OJT Coordinator or the authorized representative.ARTICLE IVEXECUTION AND PERIOD OF PERFORMANCEThe term of this Agreement shall be at the start of the Second Semester School Year 2025-2026 and will continue during the subsequent terms when there are PhilCST students who shall have been properly prepared to undergo Practicum in your company.In witness thereof, the parties have hereunto set their hands this 12th day of January, 2026 at Calasiao, Pangasinan.PHILIPPINE COLLEGE OF SCIENCE TECHNOLOGYCOMMISSION ON ELECTION URBIZTONDO                       DR. LOURDES S. FERNANDEZ${SUPERVISOR_NAME}School PresidentOfficer Head IIISigned in the Presence ofENGR. OSCAR B. GIRONELLA SR., DMinENGR. RAUL B. GIRONELLA SR., DMinExecutive Vice PresidentVice-President for Academic AffairsMS. RACHELLE N. CAMACHO, MITDean, College of Computer StudiesA C K N O W L E D G E M E N TREPUBLIC OF the PHILIPPINES)MUNICIPALITY OF CALASIAO)PROVINCE OF PANGASINAN)Before me, this _____ day of _____________ Notary Public in and for Philippine College of Sciencec and Technology, Philippines, personally appeared MRS. LOURDES S. FERNANDEZ, with the residence Certificate No________ issued at Calasiao, Pangasinan on ___________________ and executed the foregoing instruments and they acknowledged to me the same in their free will and voluntary deed.This instrument consisting of two pages including this page on which this acknowledgement is written has been read and signed by the parties and their witnesses and sealed with the notarial seal.IN WITNESS THEREOF. I/ We have hereunto sat my/our hand/s the day year above written.Doc No. ______Page No. ______BookNo. _______SeriesNo. _______
