
Endorsement Letter for On the Job Training (OJT)January 16,2026HON. JOLLY R. RESUELLOMunicipal MayorPoblacion Basista, PangasinanDear Sir/Madam:This is to introduce our bonafide student Jericho Y. Barcelon  who is a 4th year student in the program Bachelor of Science in Information Technology. He/She is now ready for his/her On-The-Job Training (OJT) for 720 hours.Considering your commitment to participate in the training of the countryΓÇÖs human resources who will join the potential manpower in our community, we are requesting for your kind assistance to accommodate our student trainee during this 2nd Semester S.Y 2025-2026 starting from January 19,2026 up to June 4,2026. We are enclosing the evaluation form, for On-The-Job Training which we request you to accomplish and provide us a copy after the training.Thank you for your favorable action to this request.More power and God bless!Very truly yours,MS. RACHELLE N. CAMACHO, MITCollege DeanApproved by:ENGR. RAUL B. GIRONELLA SR., D.Min.    Vice President for Academic Affairs
