
Endorsement Letter for On the Job Training (OJT)${CURRENT_DATE}${SUPERVISOR_NAME}${SUPERVISOR_TITLE}${COMPANY_ADDRESS}Dear Sir/Madam:This is to introduce our bonafide student ${FULL_NAME}  who is a ${YEAR_LEVEL} student in the program ${COURSE}. He/She is now ready for his/her On-The-Job Training (OJT) for 720 hours.Considering your commitment to participate in the training of the countryΓÇÖs human resources who will join the potential manpower in our community, we are requesting for your kind assistance to accommodate our student trainee during this 2nd Semester S.Y 2025-2026 starting from ${OJT_START} up to ${OJT_END}. We are enclosing the evaluation form, for On-The-Job Training which we request you to accomplish and provide us a copy after the training.Thank you for your favorable action to this request.More power and God bless!Very truly yours,MS. RACHELLE N. CAMACHO, MITCollege DeanApproved by:ENGR. RAUL B. GIRONELLA SR., D.Min.    Vice President for Academic Affairs
